secureguards.eu 2016-06-19

# Histats.com Counter ,the free web stats and stat counter, hit counter, free web tracker and tracking tools, professional and free!!

We encourage you to read this Policy carefully. If you have any questions about this Policy, our use of your Personal Information, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us. ( email is at bottom of this page ) 

We may update this Policy from time to time in our sole discretion to reflect changes in our use of your Personal Information and/or applicable law. Any changes made to this Policy will be reflected in an updated policy (denoted by an updated date above) posted on our website at [ www.histats.com.](http://www.histats.com/)

**Histats Business Customer Privacy Policy**

_Collection of Personal Information_

Customers who use the products and services available through our website (collectively, the "Services") do so voluntarily. In order to use our Services, a customer is required to create an account by registering and providing us with basic contact and website information, including, but not limited to, such customer's name, email address and website URL. By providing us with Personal Information, customers are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such Personal Information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy. 

_How We Use Personal Information_

Any Personal Information collected and stored by us is used strictly for billing purposes, contacting our customers, evaluating a prospective customer's website content, and for such other purposes as are described in this Policy. Histats does not share any customer Personal Information with any third party other than those business partners which are directly involved in managing our day to day business operations, such as, without limitation, our billing and payment processes. 

We reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information without notice or consent as it deems necessary (a) to conform to applicable law; (b) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and property; (c) to protect the safety of our users, us, or other third parties; (d) to comply with any judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us; and/or (e) pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale of assets or other business transfer. 

_Direct Email_

Our customers may voluntarily elect to receive their websites' statistical information via email. We may from time to time include important news, information, or offers within these emails. However, you may choose to opt-out of receiving any such emails, or change the frequency with which you receive such e-mails, at any time by logging on to your personal account page and changing the applicable preferences contained therein. 

_Log Files_

By accessing our website ( histats.com ), our internet servers automatically record information that your internet browser sends when you visit a website. These logs may contain information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser version, domain name, language, date and time, the referring website and information in your cookie files. 

_Third Party Advertisements_

The advertisements appearing on our website ( histats.com ) from time to time are provided by a variety of our third party advertising partners. We only share our website usage information about our users with reputable third party advertisers for the sole purpose of better targeting our website banner advertisements. 

_Histats Website Cookies_

To allow our customers the convenience of not having to remember their login information when accessing our website, Histats may place a temporary or persistent "cookie" on your computer's hard drive. These cookies are simple, harmless text files that remember the internet browser you use to access the internet. However, if you do no want to receive cookies, you may adjust the settings in your internet browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. We never collect or store any Personal Information via cookies. 

**General Internet User Privacy for our services**

Histats is a service of intangible nature which is known as Software as a Service, SaaS. The aim of this service is to measure the audience of Internet. Histats provides their customers with an IT solution via the Internet which enables them to collect statistical audience data on online mediums that is then reproduced in an aggregated and anonymous format on a web interface that only the Histats customer has access to. With this data, Histats customers can then improve the ergonomics of their own sites, as well as improving the range and quality of the products and services that they have to offer. The use of SaaS has also been adopted by the general management and the marketing, editorial or technical teams of the different companies which use our products.   
Histats reminds its customers that they must also carry out the required legal formalities and where applicable declare, with the relevant authorities, the fact that they are engaging in personal data processing concerning the data that is collected by Histats, and for which they are the proprietors. 

**Data collected by Histats**

Whenever an Internet user visits a medium that is audited by our SaaS, Histats will collect statistical data about the visit. This data provides information on an Internet user’s connection to a particular website, for example information that relates to the type of browser that is used, the number of page views, the exact path that an Internet user has taken on a site, the amount of time spent on a page, site, or information on the filling or abandonment of a shopping cart etc.   
No primary personal information such as first name, surname, telephone number, email address, etc, is collected at our own initiative by any of the Histats solutions. 

**Cookie and Unique Visitor:**  
A "cookie" is a text file which saves information relating to an Internet users browsing on the Internet. Cookies are controlled by the web browser of an Internet user’s computer. As far as Internet users are concerned, "cookies" are the best method which can be used to customise the user’s browsing on the Internet. The use of cookies means that Internet users avoid being bombarded with the same advertising messages and questions on certain sites, and they also save time on other sites, especially on sites where it is necessary to enter a login or password. As far as Histats is concerned "cookies" are used to carry out relevant and detailed statistical research. Thanks to the use of "cookies" it becomes possible to refine the analyses of JavaScript tags, and they also enable Histats customers to recognise visitors each time they visit their site (i.e. to find out that it is the same visitor without knowing who they are). These "cookies" store a unique alphanumeric ID only, relating to the device used by an Internet user, and under no circumstances is this information used to collect nominative information on the visitors. All of the results which are obtained are then compiled, and are completely anonymous. The results provide information on the browsing and behaviour of Internet users on the websites of Histats customers, information such as: the number of visitors, the number of visits, the number of page views and other information that is necessary for the effective measurement of Internet user interests. With these results it is then possible to improve the ergonomics and content of such websites. Lastly, the Histats Service can use either the cookie known as "first party" (issued by the URL of the website tracked by AT Internet) or the cookie known as "third party" (issued by a URL belonging to Histats: .histats.com ) depending on the needs of our customer. In both cases, the reason for using the cookie remains the same as the reasoning explained above and no personal data is collected via these cookies. 

**IP and geolocation:**  
During the data-collection and data-processing processes, Histats(just like any other company that exists in the fields of web analytics and web marketing) uses an Internet user’s IP address for the only purpose of geolocating the country and the city of their device , in order to identify the location in which an Internet user connects to a particular website ( level of precision: region or city in some countries ). In order to ensure better privacy protection, Histats anonymize all ip addresses: the last three digits of the IPv4 are deleted immediately, and last 64 bits on IPv6 

**Informing Internet users of the audience measurement service**  
Histats customers commit to informing Internet users who visit their sites of the existence of the data collection process that is carried out by Histats. Customers are also committed to informing such users of their access rights, right to reply, right to veto, as well as of the right to remove their personal data. For example, Histats customers can publish the following message on their site: "In order to provide our visitors with a better service, and thanks to the use of Histats solutions, we are measuring the number of page views, the number of visits, the different actions performed by visitors on our site, and the number of times visitors return to our site. If you do not wish to be audited on our site, please go to the following Histats web page that provides further information on respecting private data and follow the procedure that is available there". In addition to this Histats customers can also include an opt-out via iframe on their own internet website.

**Children's Online Privacy**

We do not do business with any person under the age of 18 and anyone using our Services must be at least 18 years of age. If we become aware that a person under the age of 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will discontinue the use of such information and remove it from our active systems. To our knowledge, we are in full compliance with all children's online privacy guidelines and practices. 

**Links to Other Websites**

Our  website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party websites and this Policy does not govern such other websites or your use of them. This Policy applies only to information collected by our website. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

(1) For a comprehensive list of definitions and what constitutes "personally identifiable information" please visit [ http://www.w3.org/TR/1998/WD-P3P10-harmonization-19980330](http://www.w3.org/TR/1998/WD-P3P10-harmonization-19980330)

(2) For more information Regarding Cookies please see - [ http://www.bbbonline.org/UnderstandingPrivacy/toolbox/cookies.asp](http://www.bbbonline.org/UnderstandingPrivacy/toolbox/cookies.asp)

Additional Information Regarding Online Privacy Can Be Found At: [ http://www.privacyalliance.org/](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)  

**Histats.com is a part of**  
Wisecode SRL  
further information about out privacy policy can be requested to : 

##  [Check your opt-out status](http://www.histats.com/optOut.php)
